{
    "subject": "resource/Rolo_Tomassi",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Band",
    "human_readable": "Rolo Tomassi is a band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9380058646202087,
            "question": "Is Rolo Tomassi a solo artist or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8391790390014648,
            "question": "Who are the members of Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218533396720886,
            "question": "What other bands are similar to Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7715369462966919,
            "question": "What genre of music does Rolo Tomassi play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7379581332206726,
            "question": "Where is Rolo Tomassi from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7310093641281128,
            "question": "When was Rolo Tomassi formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6789217591285706,
            "question": "Where can you listen to Rolo Tomassi's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.610682487487793,
            "question": "What is the name of Rolo Tomassi's latest album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6046668887138367,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46609732508659363,
            "question": "Has Rolo Tomassi won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rolo Tomassi is a band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5573_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by Rolo Tomassi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5573_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Rolo Tomassi's latest album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5573_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you listen to Rolo Tomassi's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5573_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5573_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Rolo Tomassi is a band\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five documents mention Rolo Tomassi as a musical entity, with descriptions such as \"band\", \"experimental metal band\", \"mathcore band\", and so on. While some documents may describe them as difficult to categorize or pigeonhole into a specific genre, they are consistently referred to as a band. Therefore, the triple \"Rolo Tomassi is a band\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Rolo Tomassi being a band, supporting the statement that Rolo Tomassi is a band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}